# **Matt Lucas**

## Summary

San Francisco Bay Area Senior Email Developer with nine years experience in digital marketing. Extensive, hands-on experience with coding responsive HTML emails and digital marketing assets for clients such as Intel and Autodesk, as well as building automated marketing campaigns in Marketo, Eloqua and Pardot.

# **Experience**

#### **Email Marketing Developer / PubNub**

AUGUST 2016 - PRESENT / SAN FRANCISCO, CA

# Senior Email Developer / Pierry Software

MAY 2016 - JULY 2016 / REDWOOD CITY, CA

Client Work: NetJets, San Jose Earthquakes, IMAX, Postmates, Uber

# Digital Marketing Engineer / Teradata Interactive

MAY 2014 - APRIL 2016 / SAN FRANCISCO, CA

Client Work: Procter & Gamble, Autodesk, Intel, Hertz, 7-Eleven, Brocade

#### **HTML Production Engineer / Ozone Online**

SEPTEMBER 2013 - MAY 2014 / SAN FRANCISCO, CA

Client Work: Brocade, Intel, Medtronic, JPMorgan Chase & Co., Autodesk

#### **Web Producer / OpenMarketing**

DECEMBER 2012 - JUNE 2013 / SAN FRANCISCO, CA

Client Work: PresenceLearning, Social Fluency, LiveHive, Kriste Michelini Interiors

#### Contact

510-318-4985 mattdavidlucas@gmail.com mattdavidlucas.com linkedin.com/in/mattdavidlucas

# **Marketing Platforms**

Marketo

Eloqua

Pardot

Salesforce Marketing Cloud (ExactTarget)
Teradata Marketing Applications

### **Dev/Production Skills**

Responsive HTML Email Development

**Email Client Testing via Litmus** 

Marketing Automation

Adobe Photoshop CC

HTML

CSS & Sass

JavaScript & jQuery

PHP

Linux Command Line

# **Education & Certifications**

California College of the Arts

Bachelor of Fine Arts, 2003 - 2007

Salesforce Marketing Cloud & Marketo Certified

Web Production & Design Manager / Bulldog Reporter

JANUARY 2010 - DECEMBER 2012 / OAKLAND, CA